http://www.edta.org/privacypolicy

Skip to main content (Press Enter).
Sign in
Skip auxiliary navigation (Press Enter).
Home
Skip main navigation (Press Enter).
Toggle navigation
Content types
AnnouncementsBlogsCommunitiesDiscussionsEventsGlossarySite ContentLibraries
Date range
on this day
between these dates
Posted by
Membership What is EdTA?Join EdTAHow EdTA Membership Benefits YouThespian Troupe MembershipThe International Thespian SocietyChaptersOrganizational MembershipManage a chapterActive troupe listDistinguished ThespiansEdTA Hall of FameThespian AlumniCommunity HomeOpen ForumBrowse CommunitiesBlogsMember DirectoryMentor MatchPrograms Awards, Grants, and ScholarshipsInternational Thespian Excellence AwardsTheatre in Our SchoolsJumpStart TheatreProfessional Development IntensivesITS Student LeadershipTOTS EatDemocracyworksNext Generation WorksEvents Thespian Nation LiveVirtual International Thespian FestivalEdTA National ConferenceEdTA Leadership SummitBroadway Back to SchoolThespians Go Hollywood2020-21 Events CalendarPublications DramaticsDramatics.orgTeaching TheatreAdvertisingAdvocacy Rapid Response Advocacy CenterLocalStateNational advocacy Projects and issuesEdTA Model Curriculum Framework ProjectResearch and reportsOrganizationsRecommendations for Reopening Theatre Programs GuideGuide to ESSALandscape surveyGuide to Building an Arts Education Advocacy DayDonate Make a donationEducational Theatre FoundationClub 29The Legacy Circle2019 DonorsDisaster reliefResources Theatre Educator Pro LearningEducationPlay surveyLibrariesCareer CenterTheatre Educator Evaluation WorkbookOpportunity-to-Learn StandardsStandards resourcesAbout NewsMission Diversity and InclusionCore ValuesHistoryCodes and policies Misconduct PolicyContact usBoard of DirectorsMeet EdTA's Executive DirectorMarketing opportunitiesAnnual ReportSponsorsStore Thespian Spirit ShopTrophy storeInduction Ceremony Supplies, Pins, Stickers, and MoreThespian and Junior Thespian honors
Privacy Policy and Terms of Use
Privacy Policy and Terms of Use
Privacy policy
The Educational Theatre Association cares about your privacy. We want to tell you in detail about the Internet policies and practices which we have adopted to protect your privacy so that you can feel confident about how we handle the personal information you entrust to us online.
It’s a good idea to check our privacy policy from time to time when you visit our site. Any change in our privacy policy will be prospective only. We will not make any changes that have retroactive effect unless legally required to do so.
When do we collect personal information?
We only collect personally identifiable data, such as names, addresses, email addresses, when voluntarily submitted by a visitor. Visitors may choose to submit personal information, to obtain information or submit a comment, to register for our discussion forums, or to place an order. If you are under the age of thirteen we are not allowed, by the current laws governing personally identifiable information on the Internet, to solicit or retain any information from you.
What do we do with the information?
Providing personal information is up to you, our visitor or member. We will collect personally identifiable information to email you with updates and news, to respond to your questions or comments, to register you for certain features, and to send out brochures and other information on our services and events. We offer visitors and members an “opt-out” option at any time they wish to cease receiving emails or other information from us. Visitors and members may “opt-out” by replying to an email with “UNSUBSCRIBE” in the topic, or you may contact us by email.
We do not release email addresses to third-party vendors, but may deliver carefully screened offers and information on behalf of selected organizations. Information is primarily used by us, our agents, or business partners to respond to your requests and to better serve you.
How do we use cookies?
We use cookie technology and IP addresses only to obtain non-personal information from online visitors to provide them with the best possible personalized online experience. To do this we do keep track of the type of browser (e.g., Chrome, Firefox, Internet Explorer, etc.) and operating system (e.g., Windows, Mac) used by the visitor, and the domain name of the visitor’s Internet service provider. We also track the total number of visitors to our site in an aggregate form to allow us to update and improve our site; personally identifiable information is not extracted in this process. This helps us keep our site fresh and interesting to the majority of our visitors. Cookie technology also helps us deliver content tailored to a visitor’s interests. You may disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do disable cookies, we may be unable to optimize your visit to our site.
Is credit card transaction information secure?
We use SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) to communicate with your browser software when you order from us online. SSL is the industry standard security protocol, which makes it extremely difficult for anyone else to intercept your credit card transaction and order information that you send us. Otherwise, the transmission of information to and from us is not encrypted or secure.
What do you do to safeguard personal information?
We have instituted safeguards to check that our internal procedures meet our high policy standards. We also use our best efforts to be sure that third parties who work with us agree to protect personal information that they must access in order to serve our site and our visitors.
Copyright notice
Entire contents copyright 2019 by the Educational Theatre Association. Bylined articles and credited photographs are also protected by the author’s or photographer’s copyright.
Permission is granted for the reproduction of limited numbers of copies of material on this website by teachers for classroom use, as provided under the Fair Use Doctrine. All other rights are strictly reserved.
Trademark notice
The names Educational Theatre Association, International Thespian Society, Dramatics, and the Educational Theatre Foundation and associated images are protected trademarks registered with the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office.
What about links to other sites?
We offer links to other sites, and try to link only with sites that share our values. Nevertheless, we are not responsible for the content or information collection policies of other sites. If you visit another site, you should review their privacy and other policies.
Anything else I should know?
We reserve the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request, to protect the integrity of the site, to fulfill your requests, or to cooperate in any legal investigation.
What should I do if I have questions?
If you would like us to update, change, or delete information we have about you (subject to any applicable legal exceptions), would like to opt out of receiving further information, or have questions about our privacy policy, please contact us by email.
You may also write or call us at:
Web Content ManagerEdTA4805 Montgomery RdSuite 400Cincinnati, OH 45212Phone: 513.421.3900
Contact UsCode of ConductPrivacy Policy and Terms of Use
Copyright ©
Educational Theatre Association. All rights reserved.
Powered by Higher Logic
